Bluetooth channel so you will see today
's tweet setup on which let's start this video first of all
if we talk about us ma
then yesterday also you saw a
record rally in the market due to which
we can see here Next its new
life time high from 1100
subscribe while we can see 9080 video
then subscribe its 10 to 12
if we talk about why record then
today Atul and Total Mobile who
International Peroxide subscribe and Chinese
abs
if we talk about gym then
today Tower Polyplex coming truck is absolutely
Operation Century Textiles and
some important companies from IndusInd Bank
keep their eye on the company doing their gym
so if tomorrow
we talk about why alarm sleep then here we
can see LIC Housing Finance under whose
leadership this time we got three points you can
see 4% on the left side when skin
subscribe it 10 but this is a good thing
because on this side of it subscribe
But due to investment,
a record jump has been
seen in the provisioning in it, so in future if its
provisioning amount decreases, then
we can see an improvement in its profitability and its interest income. At
this
time, if Arvind talks about this, this time the
net profit of the company is 100%, subscribe to this,
in the last six the EBITDA margin of the company is
six and its almost the
highest point night fall can be seen here,
which was 48.2 in the last year SIM card,
if we
subscribe, then the net profit of the company
in 06 2011, which
we can see in this video,
is zero as compared to the last and here it was
subscribed due to excise duty,
due to this, in its net profit,
in the scan here, we have seen this for at this time,
so you can subscribe to our channel, for this
you have to come in the description,
if we talk about these ads, then
here  But we will get
a deposit in almost stopped, only a flat in Ambedkar Nagar
can be seen here and now
you can see here that it is still
subscribed in the market, if we talk about it here,
and we
see a slight decline in open interest on IndusInd Bank,
that we
can see here, so here we subscribe to my
channel, so the first thing that we should do is
subscribe to subscribe, here
accused 01,
if this position is completed then its
total ownership will be 3%, so you will get a
little turmeric in the market today,
subscribe and keep doing this process,
subscribe to this public buying,
Chennai price is planned here by removing the peel and
similarly, it
cannot be subscribed on Monday
that if this description is successful
then the promoters can add 1.5
% here, so you can talk a little about it in the market, on
one side here we will
talk about
a subsidiary of the company which is Bloody  Chanakya,
due to this notice of an American Law Department, it is going to impose
a limit of 10 million dollars in the market,
due to which today we may have some
negative sentiment
abroad, if we talk
about the features, then it has recently
noted a payment toilet of 10 million dollars,
you should keep an eye on this also, finally if we
talk about subscribing,
you will see it in the next two-three days,
subscribe, like and share,
if you subscribe, subscribe,
thank you.